gauhati.ac.in 2014-09-03

# Gauhati University | Credits and Disclaimer

**Privacy Policy**  
We value the trust you place in _gauhati.ac.in_. Please read this Privacy Policy, which tells you what information we collect from users of the _gauhati.ac.in_ , how we use that information, and with whom we may share it. Unless defined in this Privacy Policy Conduct, terms capitalized but not defined herein are defined in the Terms & Conditions. In this Privacy Policy _gauhati.ac.in_ is referred to as " **we** ," " **us** ," or " **our** " and you the end user are referred to as " **you** ", " **your** " or “ **user** ”.

**How Personal Information Is Collected and Updated**  
We may collect information that personally identifies you when you register, when you participate in reviews and other features or when you otherwise communicate with us.

**Types of Personal Information Collected**  
We may collect the following types of information at the _gauhati.ac.in_ :

1.      When you register at any of the _gauhati.ac.in_ , we may request the following personal information:

Your name, email address, contact nos.

2.      When you search anything on the website, your keywords will be collected in a protected location for improving our search results.

**How Information Is Used and Shared**

**Processing Payments:**  
For credit card purchasers, we redirect to the relevant financial institution for online transaction and billing information.

**Legal Requirements:**  
_gauhati.ac.in_ reserves the right to disclose your personal information as necessary to:

  1. Comply with the law or comply with legal process served on _gauhati.ac.in_.
  2. Protect and defend the rights or property of _gauhati.ac.in_.
  3. Protect the personal safety of other _gauhati.ac.in_ users or the public
  4. To ensure compliance with our Terms & Conditions. _gauhati.ac.in_ co-operates with law enforcement and other third parties to enforce laws, intellectual property, and other rights, and we reserve the right to report any information related to suspicion of illegal activity to law enforcement for prosecution.

**Third Parties**  
Except as described in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose your personal information to third parties. _gauhati.ac.in_ may, however, use for its own purposes, aggregate information that does not identify you personally, or share aggregate information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties.

**Business Transfers**  
Information about _gauhati.ac.in_ users, including personal information, may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, debt financing, sale of company assets, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership in which personal information could be transferred to third parties as one of the business assets of _gauhati.ac.in_.

**Non-personal User Information**  
An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Internet. When you request pages from _gauhati.ac.in_ , our servers log your computer's IP address. _gauhati.ac.in_ collects these IP addresses for the sole purpose of identifying our users' service providers (whether yahoo, hotmail, Gmail etc.) so we can better develop our offerings at the _gauhati.ac.in_. We do not automatically link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, however we can and will use IP addresses to identify users when we feel it is necessary to:

  1. Comply with the law or comply with legal process served on _gauhati.ac.in_
  2. Protect and defend the rights or property of _gauhati.ac.in_
  3. Protect the personal safety of other _gauhati.ac.in_ users or the public
  4. To ensure compliance with our Terms & Conditions.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small packet of information that we place on your computer's hard drive whenever you visit the _gauhati.ac.in_. For each user, our web server automatically recognizes the following:

  * The host origin of the request (e.g., your IP address)
  * The referrer (e.g., where you came from if you arrived at our site via a link)
  * The requested document (e.g., the page being viewed)
  * your browser type (e.g., Internet Explorer 6.0)
  * platform information (e.g., Windows 2000, Windows XP, MAC OS 10)
  * session data (e.g., whether login was successful)

_Gauhati.ac.in_ uses cookies for a variety of reasons, including without limitation the following:

  * For session variables, to facilitate your navigation of content on the _gauhati.ac.in_.
  * To determine if cookies are enabled in your browser so that we may ensure that our _gauhati.ac.in_ run on your computer.
  * To authenticate your access to content on the _gauhati.ac.in_.

We do not store in cookies any passwords or credit card information, any information that personally identifies you.

**Steps You Can Take to Protect Your Privacy**

**What You Disclose:**  
Please take appropriate precautions not to reveal your personal information while interacting with other users on _gauhati.ac.in_. Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online - for example, via _gauhati.ac.in_ review feature - that information can be viewed and used by people that you do not know, including but not limited to other users who access at the _gauhati.ac.in_.

**Passwords:**  
Your access to your account is password-protected and only you are authorized to access it and view the information relevant to the account. You agree not to share your passwords with anyone. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords. You agree to sign off from the gauhati.ac.in and close your Internet browser window when you have finished accessing and using any website.

No Guarantee of Security. No data transmission over the Internet is guaranteed to be secure. Gauhati.ac.in does not ensure or warrant the security of any personal or other information you transmit to us including without limitation via the _gauhati.ac.in_.

**Contact Information**  
If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy; please contact our support at  **payments** **@gauhati.ac.in**
